[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You would use SMTP to send email messages.", "correct_answer": "Simple Mail Transfer Protocol", "incorrect_answers": ["Snail Mail Transfer Protocol", "Super Mail Transfer Procedure", "Standard Mail Transfer Protocol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following vitamins is known as Folic Acid?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B9", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B6", "Vitamin B2", "Vitamin B5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is Bruce Vito the uncle of professional skateboarder Bam Margera, who is famous as a member of the Jackass crew?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these places natural pearl hunting on a large scale has survived until modern times?", "correct_answer": "Australia and Bahrain", "incorrect_answers": ["India and China", "Spain", "Africa and South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Gold Rush, Georgia Hale plays the role of the showgirl, a role originally written for this actress.", "correct_answer": "Lita Grey", "incorrect_answers": ["Lolita Parker", "Lillian McMurray", "Edna Purviance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Blazing Saddles character got shot in the foot for using the cliche We will head them off at the pass?", "correct_answer": "Taggart", "incorrect_answers": ["Lyle", "Mongo", "Bart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Woody Woodpecker appeared in the 1950 sci-fi film Rocketship X-M.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the actors who portrayed the Brothers Grimm, Wilhelm and Jacob, in the 2005 movie of the same name.", "correct_answer": "Matt Damon and Heath Ledger", "incorrect_answers": ["Jude Law and Heath Ledger", "Jude Law and Jake Gyllenhaal", "Matt Damon and Jake Gyllenhaal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What essential nutrient is plain yogurt rich in?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B2", "Vitamin B12", "Vitamin B6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these would most likely appear on a prescription if the medication should be taken as a large single dose?", "correct_answer": "bol.", "incorrect_answers": ["prn", "A.A.O.", "q.i.d"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The character played by which of these actors/actresses did not survive in the disaster movie The Towering Inferno?", "correct_answer": "Robert Wagner", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve McQueen", "Susan Blakely", "Paul Newman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1982, this major Japanese car manufacturer was the first one to begin production of Japanese cars in the USA.", "correct_answer": "Honda", "incorrect_answers": ["Mazda", "Toyota", "Mitsubishi"]}]